Guide to the Building Trades Employers Association Records WAG.196
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Building Trades Employers Association Records
circa 1897-2011
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Building Trades Employers' Association
Coletti, Louis J.
WAG.196
56.25 Linear Feet in 56 record cartons and 1 oversize folder
The Building Trades Employers Association (BTEA) was founded in 1903 to coordinate the response of employers in the building trades to union demands and labor unrest, and to establish a joint arbitration plan for the industry. The collection is primarily comprised of BTEA contracts, mediation, and arbitration files. It also contains minutes of meetings of the BTEA Board of Governors, convention files, correspondence, and a small number of photographs, newsletters and clippings.
Historical/Biographical Note
The Building Trades Employers Association (NYC) traces its origins to the Building Trades Club, which began meeting in 1888. The organization gradually changed in nature from a social club to a more business-oriented model, and adopted its current name in 1903. The aims of the organization were to coordinate the response of employers in the building trades to union demands and labor unrest, and to establish a joint arbitration plan for the industry. Initially more than 2,000 contractors and 33 craft associations responded to the call to form the BTEA. Strong union opposition to centralized arbitration of disputes was eventually overcome, and the unions agreed to curtailment of their business agents' powers and the prohibition of sympathy strikes and unofficial local strikes. After a number of conflicts, and the temporary expulsion of several unions, the situation stabilized; by 1922 agreements were commonly bargained under the auspices of the BTEA and, on the unions' behalf, the newly formed Building Trades Council. A unique feature of New York City's arbitration arrangements in the industry is the fact that final determinations in juridictional disputes are made by the BTEA.
After the building booms of the 1950s and 1960s, the construction industry in New York has experienced frequent periods of contraction and structural change. The prevalence of specialized work (such as renovation) typically handled by small contracts, and the inroads of non-union contractors have posed a challenge to the establishied structure of labor-management arrangements established by the BTEA and BTC.
Arrangement
The collection has been divided into three series; most files are in original order. Series 1 contains nine boxes of contracts, which are arranged by union name. Series 2 is comprised of mediations, arbitrations, and other documents created between 1903-1995. Arbitrations in Series 2 are coded according to the listing of decisions in the Handbook of the Building Trades Employers Association of the City of New York (commonly known as the "Green Book"; copy at Tamiment Library, call no. HD6515 B9 N73 1990).
Series 3 contians 11 boxes of mediation and arbitration files between 1989 and 2011, which are numbered and grouped in a roughly chronological order. The majority of the files were created after 2000 and have been numbered in a way that reflects the date in which proceedings begun. Files created prior to 2000, however, are dated but lack numeration.
Scope and Content Note
The collection is primarily comprised of BTEA contracts, mediation, and arbitration files. It also contains minutes of meetings of the BTEA Board of Governors, convention files, correspondence, and a small number of photographs, newsletters and clippings. The extensive arbitration files contain a wide range of materials used by The Arbitration Board in the process of reaching a decision, including court papers, correspondence, notes, blueprints, photographs, construction job lists and manufacturers' circulars.
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open without restrictions.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
Donated by the Building Trades Employers Association, under an agreement with its Chairman, Louis J. Coletti, in 1999. The accession numbers associated with this gift are 1978.002 and 1978.003. An additional gift of 11 boxes was made in 2013. The accession number associated with this donation is 2013.024.
The accession numbers 1950.094 and 1978.015 are also associated with this collection.
Custodial History
The archived website was migrated from the California Digital Library's Web Archiving Service to the Internet Archive's Archive-It Service in November 2015. The link to California Digital Library was removed in October 2017.
Arbitration files.; Contracts; Construction industry -- New York (State) -- New York.; Building trades |x Employees |z New York (State) |z New York.; Minutes (administrative records); Correspondence.; Building Trades Employers' Association; Building Trades Employers' Association; Coletti, Louis J.
- Series I: Contracts, 1903-1993; 9 Linear Feet 9 Record Cartons
  - Contracts- Asbestos Workers and Asbestos Employers, 1916-1947 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Contracts- Asbestos Workers and Asbestos Employers, 1950-1958 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Contracts- Asbestos Workers and Asbestos Employers, 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Contracts- Asbestos Workers and Asbestos Employers, 1969-1990 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Contracts- Asphalt Employers and Asphalt Workers, 1932 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Contracts- Asphalt Employers and Asphalt Workers, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Contracts- Blasters (record), 1916-1929 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Contracts- Blasters (record), 1929-1932 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Contracts- Blasters (record), 1935-1938 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Contracts- Blasters (record), 1946-1948 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Contracts- Bldg. Maintenance Craftsmen Rockefeller Center Inc., 1938-1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Contracts- Boilermakers and Ironworkers, 1919-1950 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Contracts- Boilermakers and Ironworkers, 1957-1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Contracts- Boilermakers and Ironworkers, 1969-1978 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Contracts- Boilermakers and Ironworkers, 1978-1990 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Contracts- Bricklayers' Helpers (Mason Tenders), 1929-1937 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Contracts- Bricklayers' Helpers (Mason Tenders), 1939-1949 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Contracts- Bricklayers' Helpers (Mason Tenders), 1950-1957 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Contracts- Bricklayers' Helpers (Mason Tenders), 1960-1969 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Contracts- Bricklayers' Helpers (Mason Tenders), 1969-1978 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Contracts- Bricklayers' Helpers (Mason Tenders), 1978-1990 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Contracts-Bricklayers and Mason Builders, 1922-1940 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Contracts-Bricklayers and Mason Builders, 1940-1949 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Contracts-Bricklayers and Mason Builders, 1949-1950 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Contracts-Bricklayers and Mason Builders, 1950-1960 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Contracts-Bricklayers and Mason Builders, 1960-1966 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Contracts-Bricklayers and Mason Builders, 1967-1979 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Contracts-Bricklayers and Mason Builders, 1978-1986 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Contracts- Carpenters and Master Carpenters Joint Trade Committee, 1916-1940 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Contracts- Carpenters and Master Carpenters Joint Trade Committee, 1940-1948 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Contracts- Carpenters and Master Carpenters Joint Trade Committee, 1950-1954 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Contracts- Carpenters and Master Carpenters Joint Trade Committee, 1955-1960 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Contracts- Carpenters and Master Carpenters Joint Trade Committee, 1960-1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Contracts- Carpenters and Master Carpenters Joint Trade Committee, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Contracts- Carpenters and Master Carpenters Joint Trade Committee, 1975-1987 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Contracts- Carpenters and Master Carpenters Joint Trade Committee, 1987-1990 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Contracts- Carpet and Linoleum Mechanics Union 67 Agreement, 1947-1949 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Contracts- Carpet and Linoleum Mechanics Union 67 Agreement, 1949-1957 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Contracts- Carpet and Linoleum Mechanics Union 67 Agreement, 1964-1969 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Contracts- Carpet and Linoleum Mechanics Union 67 Agreement, 1969-1978 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Contracts- Carpet and Linoleum Mechanics Union 67 Agreement, 1981-1987 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Contracts- Carpet and Linoleum Mechanics Union 67 Agreement, 1932-1939 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Contracts- Carpet and Linoleum Mechanics Union 67 Agreement, 1942-1947 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Contracts- Cement Masons and The Cement League, 1916-1942 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Contracts- Cement Masons and The Cement League, 1950-1959 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Contracts- Cement Masons and The Cement League, 1960-1971 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Contracts- Cement Masons and The Cement League, 1972-1978 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Contracts- Cement Masons and The Cement League, 1980-1989 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Contracts- Cement Masons and The Cement League (contract books), 1981-1993 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Contracts- Cement Masons and The Cement League, 1916-1942 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Contracts- Cement Masons and The Cement League, 1950-1959 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Contracts- Cement Masons and The Cement League, 1960-1971 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Contracts- Cement Masons and The Cement League, 1972-1978 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Contracts- Cement Masons and The Cement League, 1980-1989 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Contracts- Cement Masons and The Cement League (contract books), 1981-1993 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Contracts- Contractors Protective Assistance Agreement (All), 1947-1952 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Contracts- Decorative Glass Workers and Stained Glass Employers, 1927-1937 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Contracts- Decorative Glass Workers and Stained Glass Employers, 1940-1949 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Contracts- Derrickmen and Stone Setter Employers, 1926-1946 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Contracts- Derrickmen and Stone Setter Employers, 1946-1970 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Contracts- Derrickmen and Stone Setter Employers, 1970-1990 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Contracts- Dockbuilders Assn. Agreement (All), 1922-1929 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Contracts- Dockbuilders Assn. Agreement (All), 1934-1950 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Contracts- Dockbuilders Assn. Agreement (All), 1957-1960 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Contracts- Dockbuilders Assn. Agreement (All), 1963-1969 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers, 1924-1927 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers, 1930-1934 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers, 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers, 1940-1942 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers, 1950-1961 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers, 1963-1967 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers and Employers, 1903-1923 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers and Employers, 1924-1928 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers and Employers, 1934-1938 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers and Employers, 1940-1945 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers and Employers, 1946-1948 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers and Employers, 1950-1958 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers and Employers, 1959-1969 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers and Employers, 1970-1974 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers and Employers, 1977-1980 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers and Employers, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Contracts- Electrical Workers and Employers, 1986-1992 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Contracts- Elevator Constructors and Employer, 1956-1972 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Contracts- Elevator Constructors and Employer, 1975-1982 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Contracts- Elevator Constructors and Employer, 1981-1987 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Contracts- Engineers and General Contractors, 1960-1963 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Contracts- Engineers and General Contractors, 1963-1969 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Contracts- Engineers and General Contractors (part 1), 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Contracts- Engineers and General Contractors (part 2), 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Contracts- Engineers- Iron League Structure. Steel Erectors, 1923-1931 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Contracts- Engineers- Iron League Structure. Steel Erectors, 1940-1966 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Contracts- Engineers Local 15A, 1955-1959 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Contracts- Engineers Local 15A, 1960-1972 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Contracts- Engineers Local 15A, 1970-1975 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Contracts- Engineers Local 15A, 1975-1977 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Contracts- Engineers Local 15A, 1978-1984 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Contracts- Engineers Local 15A, 1984-1990 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Contracts- Engineers Local 15C, 1938-1941 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Contracts- Engineers Local 15C, 1947-1953 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Contracts- Engineers Local 15C, 1957-1965 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Contracts- Engineers Local 15D, 1961-1969 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Contracts- Engineers Local 15D, 1969-1978 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Contracts- Engineers Local 15D, 1978-1990 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Contracts- Engineers/Misc. Allied/GCA/#94, 1926-1928 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Contracts- Engineers/Misc. Allied/GCA/#94, 1931-1938 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Contracts- Engineers/Misc. Allied/GCA/#94, 1946-1957 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Contracts- Engineers/Misc. Allied/GCA/#94, 1960-1969 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Contracts- Engineers/Misc. Allied/GCA/#94, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Contracts- Engineers/Misc. Allied/GCA/#94, 1972-1975 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Contracts- Engineers/Misc. Allied/GCA/#94, 1975-1981 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Contracts- Engineers/Misc. Allied/GCA/#94, 1978-1983 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Contracts- Engineers/Misc. Allied/GCA/#94, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Contracts- Engineers/Misc. Allied/GCA/#94, 1987-1993 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Contracts- Excavating Laborers, 1930-1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Contracts- Excavating Laborers, 1950-1959 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Contracts- Excavating Laborers, 1960-1969 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Contracts- Excavating Laborers, 1969-1978 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Contracts- Excavating Laborers, 1978-1993 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Contracts- Glaziers and Glass Dealers, 1921-1940 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Contracts- Glaziers and Glass Dealers, 1950-1954 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Contracts- Glaziers and Glass Dealers, 1955-1958 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Contracts- Glaziers and Glass Dealers, 1960-1969 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Contracts- Glaziers and Glass Dealers, 1969-1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Contracts- Glaziers and Glass Dealers, 1975-1990 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Contracts- Granite Cutters, 1924-1944 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Contracts- Granite Cutters, 1948-1972 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Contracts- Highway, Road and Street Construction Laborers, 1972-1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Contracts- House Shorers' Union and House Movers-(Old), 1924 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Contracts- House Wreckers' Union Local 95, 1957 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Contracts- House Wreckers' Union Local 95, 1963-1969 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Contracts- House Wreckers' Union Local 95, 1969-1972 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Contracts- Ironworkers Local 455, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Contracts- Ironworkers Local 455, 1941-1948 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Contracts- Ironworkers Local 455, 1950-1953 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Contracts- Ironworkers Local 455, 1954-1960 (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Contracts- Ironworkers Local 455, 1967-1988 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Contracts- Iron Workers, Local Union #580, 1923-1928 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Contracts- Iron Workers, Local Union #580, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Contracts- Iron Workers, Local Union #580, 1940-1948 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Contracts- Iron Workers, Local Union #580, 1950-1953 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Contracts- Iron Workers, Local Union #580, 1955-1969 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Contracts- Iron Workers, Local Union #580, 1969-1978 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Contracts- Iron Workers, Local Union #580, 1978-1993 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - Contracts- Iron Workers, Structural, L.U. 40 and 361, 1958-1963 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Contracts- Iron Workers, Structural, L.U. 40 and 361, 1966-1969 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Contracts- Iron Workers, Structural, L.U. 40 and 361, 1970-1977 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Contracts- Iron Workers, Structural, L.U. 40 and 361, 1978-1991 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Contracts- Laborers-Concrete and Cement League, 1929-1947 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Contracts- Laborers-Concrete and Cement League, 1950-1975 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Contracts- Laborers-Concrete and Cement League, 1960-1969 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Contracts- Laborers-Concrete and Cement League, 1970-1978 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Contracts- Laborers-Concrete and Cement League, 1978-1990 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Contracts- Marble Workers and Marble Industry Employers, 1932-1946 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Contracts- Marble Workers and Marble Industry Employers, 1950-1960 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Contracts- Marble Workers and Marble Industry Employers, 1962-1971 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Contracts- Marble Workers and Marble Industry Employers, 1972-1977 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Contracts- Marble Workers and Marble Industry Employers, 1979-1991 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Contracts- Metallic lathers and Cement League, 1918-1941 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Contracts- Metallic lathers and Cement League, 1950-1960 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Contracts- Metallic lathers and Cement League, 1960-1969 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Contracts- Metallic lathers and Cement League, 1969-1974 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Contracts- Metallic lathers and Cement League, 1976-1979 (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Contracts- Metallic lathers and Cement League, 1982-1993 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Contracts- Metallic lathers and Cement League, 1926-1938 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Contracts- Metallic lathers and Cement League, 1941-1950 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Contracts- Metallic lathers and Cement League, 1950-1960 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Contracts- Metallic lathers and Cement League, 1960-1969 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Contracts- Metallic lathers and Cement League, 1969-1981 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Contracts- Metallic lathers and Cement League, 1982-1990 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Contracts- Millwright (Carpenters), 1960-1972 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Contracts- Millwright (Carpenters), 1972-1984 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Contracts- Mosaic Employers with Workers and Helpers, 1926-1933 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Contracts- Mosaic Employers with Workers and Helpers, 1936-1946 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Contracts- Mosaic Employers with Workers and Helpers, 1948-1963 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Contracts- Mosaic Employers with Workers and Helpers, 1966-1975 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Contracts- Mosaic Employers with Workers and Helpers, 1982-1990 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Contracts- Operating Engineers, 1969-1972 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Contracts- Painters, Boss and Union (Brooklyn), 1926-1928 (Box 6, Folder 15)
  - Contracts- Painters, Boss and Union (Brooklyn), 1931-1937 (Box 6, Folder 16)
  - Contracts- Painters, Boss and Union (Brooklyn), 1949-1957 (Box 6, Folder 17)
  - Contracts- Painters, Boss and Union (Brooklyn), 1963-1989 (Box 6, Folder 18)
  - Contracts- Painters, Master and Union, 1926-1928 (Box 6, Folder 19)
  - Contracts- Painters, Master and Union, 1929-1933 (Box 6, Folder 20)
  - Contracts- Painters, Master and Union, 1934-1937 (Box 6, Folder 21)
  - Contracts- Painters, Master and Union, 1937-1945 (Box 6, Folder 22)
  - Contracts- Painters, Master and Union, 1947-1948 (Box 6, Folder 23)
  - Contracts- Painters, Master and Union, 1950-1959 (Box 6, Folder 24)
  - Contracts- Painters, Master and Union, 1962-1965 (Box 6, Folder 25)
  - Contracts- Painters, Master and Union, 1968-1974 (Box 6, Folder 26)
  - Contracts- Painters, Master and Union, 1978-1985 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Contracts- Plasterers' Helpers, 1917-1937 (Box 6, Folder 28)
  - Contracts- Plasterers' Helpers, 1942-1946 (Box 6, Folder 29)
  - Contracts- Plasterers' Helpers, 1947-1950 (Box 6, Folder 30)
  - Contracts- Plasterers' Helpers, 1951-1959 (Box 6, Folder 31)
  - Contracts- Plasterers' Helpers, 1960-1970 (Box 6, Folder 32)
  - Contracts- Plasterers' Helpers, 1971-1978 (Box 6, Folder 33)
  - Contracts- Plasterers' Helpers, 1980-1988 (Box 6, Folder 34)
  - Contracts- Plasterers' Union and Employers Plasterer, 1915-1933 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Contracts- Plasterers' Union and Employers Plasterer, 1934-1935 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Contracts- Plasterers' Union and Employers Plasterer, 1941-1949 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Contracts- Plasterers' Union and Employers Plasterer, 1951-1960 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Contracts- Plasterers' Union and Employers Plasterer, 1962-1974 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Contracts- Plasterers' Union and Employers Plasterer, 1976-1980 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #1, 1946-1952 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #1, 1961-1963 (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #1, 1966-1975 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #1, 1984-1989 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #1, 1990-1993 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #2, 1917-1939 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #2, 1946-1948 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #2 (contract books), 1960-1970 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #2 (contract books), 1970-1976 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #2, 1976-1979 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #2 (contract books), 1979-1988 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #2, 1988-1991 (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Contracts- Plumbers' Laborers, 1949-1957 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Contracts- Plumbers' Laborers, 1963-1989 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #371, 1932-1953 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #371, 1954-1958 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #371, 1963-1976 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #371, 1977-1985 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Contracts- Plumbers, L. #371, 1985-1994 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Contracts- Pres, Local #1974, 1974-1977 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Contracts- Pres, Local #1974, 1983-1992 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Contracts- Riggers and Machinery Movers, 1919-1937 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Contracts- Riggers and Machinery Movers, 1941-1948 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Contracts- Riggers and Machinery Movers, 1950-1955 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Contracts- Riggers and Machinery Movers, 1957-1958 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Contracts- Riggers and Machinery Movers, 1960-1982 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Contracts- Roofers, Composition and Waterproofers Union, 1924-1939 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Contracts- Roofers, Composition and Waterproofers Union, 1941-1957 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Contracts- Roofers, Composition and Waterproofers Union, 1960-1969 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Contracts- Roofers, Composition and Waterproofers Union, 1972-1979 (Box 7, Folder 36)
  - Contracts- Roofers, Composition and Waterproofers Union, 1980-1990 (Box 7, Folder 37)
  - Contracts- Roofers, Slate and Tile and Roof Sheet Metal Employers, 1916-1939 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Contracts- Roofers, Slate and Tile and Roof Sheet Metal Employers, 1942-1948 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Contracts- Roofers, Slate and Tile and Roof Sheet Metal Employers, 1953-1957 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Contracts- Roofers, Slate and Tile and Roof Sheet Metal Employers, 1960-1964 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Contracts- Roofers, Slate and Tile and Roof Sheet Metal Employers, 1967-1970 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Contracts- Roofers, Slate and Tile and Roof Sheet Metal Employers, 1970-1976 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Contracts- Roofers, Slate and Tile and Roof Sheet Metal Employers, 1987-1990 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Contracts- Sheet Metal Worker and Employers, 1910-1939 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Contracts- Sheet Metal Worker and Employers, 1940-1950 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Contracts- Sheet Metal Worker and Employers, 1950-1957 (Box 8, Folder 10)